The Secret Lives of Cheerleaders is a tv movie, thriller,
drama film directed by Peter Sullivan.
A new transfer student reluctantly tries out for the cheerleading
team at the insistence of her overly ambitious mother.
Candice, played by Denise Richards.
Ava, played by Savannah May.
Katrina, played by Alexandria DeBerry.
Ms Sinclair, played by Josie Davis.
Mr. Bailey, played by Tilky Jones.
Patrick, played by Gunner Burkhardt.
Alexandra Beaton (born c.
1994) is a Canadian actress.
She is known for starring as Emily on the Canadian teen drama
series The Next Step during its first seven seasons.
The film explores themes of cheerleader, lifetime, lmn, lifetime, lifetimemovie.
The tone is emotional and intense.